globe7.com 2014-04-30

# Free VoIP| PC to PC Calling| Web Phone

### **Globe7** is a value innovation and globally patented product and Marketed by Globe7 (UK) Limited.  

**Information collection and use by Globe7**  
Globe7collects user submitted information such as name, email address, age, city etc to authenticate users and serve them better as well. Globe7 also collects other profile data including but not limited to: professional interests, gender, education and occupation in order to assist users in finding and communicating with each other. 

Globe7also logs non-personally-identifiable information including ip address, profile information, aggregate user data, and browser type, from users and visitors to the site. This data is used to manage the website, track usage and improve the website services. This non-personally-identifiable information may be shared with third-parties to provide more relevant services and advertisements to members. User ip addresses are recorded for security and monitoring purposes.

We may also use a user's email address to send updates, a newsletter or news regarding the service.  
Users may be asked to provide personal information including name, email address or postal address or to answer questions in order to participate. We may transfer personal information to certain ad partners that you have explicitly requested to receive information from. It will be clear at the point of collection who is collecting the personal information and whose privacy statement will apply.

**Security**  
Globe7member accounts are secured by member-created passwords. Globe7 takes precautions to ensure that member account information is kept private. We use reasonable measures to protect member information that is stored within our database, and we restrict access to member information to those employees who need access to perform their job functions, such as our technical staff and customer service personnel. Please note that we cannot guarantee the security of member account information. Unauthorized entry or use, hardware or software failure, and other factors may compromise the security of member information at any time. For any additional information about the security measures we use on Globe7, please contact us: admin@globe7.com 

**Sharing and disclosure of information Globe7collects**  
Except as otherwise described in this privacy statement, Globe7 will not disclose personal information to any third party unless we believe that disclosure is necessary: (1) to conform to legal requirements or to respond to a subpoena, search warrant or other legal process received by Globe7, whether or not a response is required by applicable law; (2) to enforce the Globe7 terms of use agreement or to protect our rights; or (3) to protect the safety of members of the public and users of the service.   
Globe7 reserves the right to transfer personal information to a successor in interest that acquires rights to that information as a result of the sale of Globe7 or substantially all of its assets to that successor in interest. For more information see the "changes in our privacy policy" section below. 

**Changes in our privacy policy**  
From time to time we may make changes to our privacy policy. If we make changes, we will post them on our site to make users aware of what the changes are so users will always be aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and when we may disclose it. A user is bound by any minor changes to the policy when she or he uses the site after those changes have been posted if, however, we are going to use users' personally identifiable information in a manner materially different from that stated at the time of collection we will notify by posting a notice on our web site for 30 days.

**Contacting the web site**  
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this web site, please contact us at: admin@globe7.com
